export const htmlQuestions = [
    {
        "Question": "HTML is the standard ____ language for creating Web pages?",
        "option1": "scripting",
        "option2": "programming",
        "option3": "styling",
        "answer": "markup"
    },
    {
        "Question": "HTML stands for_______?",
        "option1": "Hyperactive Text Markup Language",
        "answer": "Hyper Text Markup Language",
        "option2": "Hyper Text Machine Language",
        "option3": "None of these"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Which is the correct syntax to include comment in an HTML document?",
        "option1": "//",
        "option2": "/* Comment */",
        "option3": "// Comment //",
        "answer": "<!-- Comment -->"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Can we hide content using the comment?",
        "answer": "Yes",
        "option1": "No"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Can we hide inline content using the comment?",
        "answer": "Yes",
        "option1": "No"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Which element/tag defines a paragraph?",
        "answer": "<p>",
        "option1": "<pre>",
        "option2": "<panel>",
        "option3": "None of the above"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Which tag/element defines the HTML document's body?",
        "option1": "<HTML>",
        "option2": "<HTMLbody>",
        "option3": "<bdy>",
        "answer": "<body>"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Which tag contains the meta information about the HTML page?",
        "option1": "<html>",
        "option2": "<title>",
        "answer": "<head>",
        "option3": "<body>"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Which tag is the root element of an HTML page?",
        "answer": "<html>",
        "option1": "<title>",
        "option2": "<head>",
        "option3": "<body>"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Who invented HTML?",
        "option1": "Dave Raggett",
        "answer": "Tim Berners-Lee",
        "option2": "Denis Ritchie",
        "option3": "All of the above"
    },
    {
        "Question": "HTML tags with no content are called _____?",
        "option1": "Special tags",
        "option2": "Advanced tags",
        "answer": "Empty tags",
        "option3": "Other tags"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Nested HTML Elements are allowed in HTML?",
        "answer": "Yes",
        "option1": "No"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Is HTML a case sensitive?",
        "option1": "Yes",
        "answer": "No"
    },
    {
        "Question": "HTML headings are defined with the _____ tags?",
        "option1": "<head1> to <head6>",
        "option2": "<p1> to <p6>",
        "answer": "<h1> to <h6>",
        "option3": "<h1> to <h3>"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Which tag is used to display a horizontal rule (horizotnal line)?",
        "option1": "<br>",
        "answer": "<hr>",
        "option2": "<hr>...</hr>",
        "option3": "<line>"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is the correct syntax of <hr> tag?",
        "option1": "<hr>",
        "option2": "<hr />",
        "option3": "None of the above",
        "answer": "All of the above"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Which tag is used to define a line break?",
        "option1": "<\\n>",
        "option2": "<lr>",
        "answer": "<br>",
        "option3": "<br>...</br>"
    },
    {
        "Question": "What is the correct syntax of <br> tag?",
        "option1": "<br>",
        "option2": "<br />",
        "answer": "All of the above",
        "option3": "None of the above"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Which tag is used to define preformatted text?",
        "option1": "<pf>",
        "option2": "<p>",
        "answer": "<pre>",
        "option3": "<code>"
    },
    {
        "Question": "Which HTML attribute is used to define styles of an element?",
        "option1": "<style>",
        "option2": "<css>",
        "answer": "style",
        "option3": "css"
    },
    {
        "Question":"Which is the correct HTML statement to define the red color of the paragraph text?",
        "option1":"<p style=\"color: #ff0000;\">",
        "option2":"<p style=\"color: red;\">",
        "answer":"Both A and B.",
        "option3":"None of the above"
    },
    {
        "Question":"Which HTML tag is used to define bold text, without any extra importance?",
        "option1":"<strong>",
        "option2":"<bold>",
        "option3":"<bolder>",
        "answer":"<b>."
    },
    {
        "Question":"Which HTML tag is used to define text with strong importance?",
        "answer":"<strong>.",
        "option1":"<bold>",
        "option2":"<bolder>",
        "option3":"<b>"
    },
    {
        "Question":"Which HTML tag is used to define italic text?",
        "option1":"<italic>",
        "option2":"<em>",
        "answer":"<i>.",
        "option3":"<it>"
    },
    {
        "Question":"Which HTML tag is used to define emphasized text?",
        "option1":"<italic>",
        "answer":"<em>.",
        "option2":"<i>",
        "option3":"<it>"
    },
    {
        "Question":"Which HTML tag is used to define smaller text?",
        "option1":"<normal>",
        "option2":"<span>",
        "option3":"<smaller>",
        "answer":"<small>."
    },
    {
        "Question":"Which HTML tag is used to define marked or highlighted text?",
        "answer":"<mark>.",
        "option1":"<highlight>",
        "option2":"<m>",
        "option3":"<highlighted>"
    },
    {
        "Question":"Which HTML tag is used to define strike a line through deleted text?",
        "option1":"<delete>",
        "answer":"<del>.",
        "option2":"<deleted>",
        "option3":"<through>"
    },
    {
        "Question":"Which HTML tag is used to define underline inserted text?",
        "option1":"<underline>",
        "option2":"<text-decoration>",
        "answer":"<u>.",
        "option3":"Both C and B"
    },
    {
        "Question":"Which HTML tag is used to define subscript text?",
        "answer":"<sub>.",
        "option1":"<subscript>",
        "option2":"<s>",
        "option3":"<subscripted>"
    },
    {
        "Question":"Which HTML tag is used to define superscript text?",
        "answer":"<sup>.",
        "option1":"<superscript >",
        "option2":"<s>",
        "option3":"<superscripted>"
    },
    {
        "Question":"Which is the correct HTML statement to display H2O in a paragraph?",
        "option1":"<p>H<sup>2</sup>O</p>",
        "option2":"<p>H<ins>2</ins>O</p>",
        "option3":"<p>H<below>2</below>O</p>",
        "answer":"<p>H<sub>2</sub>O</p>."
    },
    {
        "Question":"Which is the correct HTML statement to display HelloWorld in a paragraph?",
        "answer":"<p>Hello<sup>World</sup></p>.",
        "option1":"<p>Hello<top>World</top></p>",
        "option2":"<p>Hello<sub>World</sub></p>",
        "option3":"<p>Hello<above>World</above></p>"
    },
    {
        "Question":"Which is the correct HTML statement to display HelloHi! in a paragraph?",
        "answer":"<p><del>Hello</del><ins>Hi!</ins></p>.",
        "option1":"<p><u>Hello</u><ins>Hi!</ins></p>",
        "option2":"<p><cut>Hello</cut><ins>Hi!</ins></p>",
        "option3":"All of the above"
    },
    {
        "Question":"Which is the correct HTML statement to display Hello IncludeHelp in a paragraph?",
        "option1":"<p>Hello <mark>IncludeHelp</mark></p>",
        "answer":"<p>Hello<mark>IncludeHelp</mark></p>.",
        "option2":"<p>Hello <span>IncludeHelp</span></p>",
        "option3":"<p>Hello<span>IncludeHelp</span></p>"
    }
];